```json
[
    {
    "question": "Violet",
    "answer" : ["violet","pink"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Aqua",
    "answer" : ["blue","aqua"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Yellow",
    "answer" : ["orange","yellow"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Black",
    "answer" : ["black","gray"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Biru Muda",
    "answer" : ["blue","lightblue"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Purple",
    "answer" : ["violet","purple"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Gold",
    "answer" : ["gold","brown"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Hijau Muda",
    "answer" : ["lightgreen","green"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Red",
    "answer" : ["red","orange"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Green",
    "answer" : ["blue","green"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Brown",
    "answer" : ["yellow","brown"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Biru Muda",
    "answer" : ["lightgreen","lightblue"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Hijau Muda",
    "answer" : ["lightgreen","lightblue"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "White",
    "answer" : ["black","white"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Red",
    "answer" : ["red","yellow"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Gray",
    "answer" : ["silver","gray"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Blue",
    "answer" : ["lightblue","blue"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Green",
    "answer" : ["green","lightgreen"],
    "key": 0
    },
    {
    "question": "Aqua",
    "answer" : ["red","aqua"],
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Yellow",
    "answer" : ["yellow","orang"],
    "key": 0
    },

]